<resources>
    <string name="default_hymn">
        ZAbide With Mezzzxzz
        8zzzxzz
        falsezzzxzz
"        Abide with me; fast falls the eventide;
        The darkness deepens; Lord with me abide.
        When other helpers fail and comforts flee,
        Help of the helpless, O abide with me.

        Swift to its close ebbs out life’s little day;
        Earth’s joys grow dim; its glories pass away;
        Change and decay in all around I see;
        O Thou who changest not, abide with me.

        Not a brief glance I beg, a passing word,
        But as Thou dwell’st with Thy disciples, Lord,
        Familiar, condescending, patient, free.
        Come not to sojourn, but abide with me.

        Come not in terrors, as the King of kings,
        But kind and good, with healing in Thy wings;
        Tears for all woes, a heart for every plea.
        Come, Friend of sinners, thus abide with me.

        Thou on my head in early youth didst smile,
        And though rebellious and perverse meanwhile,
        Thou hast not left me, oft as I left Thee.
        On to the close, O Lord, abide with me.

        I need Thy presence every passing hour.
        What but Thy grace can foil the tempter’s power?
        Who, like Thyself, my guide and stay can be?
        Through cloud and sunshine, Lord, abide with me.

        I fear no foe, with Thee at hand to bless;
        Ills have no weight, and tears no bitterness.
        Where is death’s sting? Where, grave, thy victory?
        I triumph still, if Thou abide with me.

        Hold Thou Thy cross before my closing eyes;
        Shine through the gloom and point me to the skies.
        Heaven’s morning breaks, and earth’s vain shadows flee;
        In life, in death, O Lord, abide with me.
        "zzzxzz
        888888
        zAm I A Soldier Of The Cross?zzzxzz
        6zzzxzz
        falsezzzxzz
"        Am I a soldier of the cross?,
        A follower of the Lamb?,
        And shall I fear to own His cause,
        Or blush to speak His Name?

        Must I be carried to the skies
        On flowery beds of ease?,
        While others fought to win the prize,
        And sailed through bloody seas?

        Are there no foes for me to face?
        Must I not stem the flood?
        Is this vile world a friend to grace,
        To help me on to God?

        Sure I must fight if I would reign;
        Increase my courage, Lord.
        I’ll bear the toil, endure the pain,
        Supported by Thy Word.

        Thy saints in all this glorious war
        Shall conquer, though they die;
        They see the triumph from afar,
        By faith’s discerning eye

        When that illustrious day shall rise,
        And all Thy armies shine
        In robes of victory through skies,
        The glory shall be Thine.
"zzzxzz
        888888
        amazing Gracezzzxzz
        7zzzxzz
        falsezzzxzz
"        Amazing grace! How sweet the sound
        That saved a wretch like me!
        I once was lost, but now am found;
        Was blind, but now I see.

        ’Twas grace that taught my heart to fear,
        And grace my fears relieved;
        How precious did that grace appear
        The hour I first believed.

        Through many dangers, toils and snares,
        I have already come;
        ’Tis grace hath brought me safe thus far,
        And grace will lead me home.

        The Lord has promised good to me,
        His Word my hope secures;
        He will my Shield and Portion be,
        As long as life endures.

        Yea, when this flesh and heart shall fail,
        And mortal life shall cease,
        I shall possess, within the veil,
        A life of joy and peace.

        The earth shall soon dissolve like snow,
        The sun forbear to shine;
        But God, Who called me here below,
        Shall be forever mine.

        When we’ve been there ten thousand years,
        Bright shining as the sun,
        We’ve no less days to sing God’s praise
        Than when we’d first begun.
"zzzxzz
        888888
        Are You Washed In The Blood?zzzxzz
        4zzzxzz
        truezzzxzz
"        Have you been to Jesus for the cleansing power?
        Are you washed in the blood of the Lamb?
        Are you fully trusting in His grace this hour?
        Are you washed in the blood of the Lamb?

        Are you washed in the blood,
        In the soul cleansing blood of the Lamb?
        Are your garments spotless? Are they white as snow?
        Are you washed in the blood of the Lamb?

        Are you walking daily by the Savior’s side?
        Are you washed in the blood of the Lamb?
        Do you rest each moment in the Crucified?
        Are you washed in the blood of the Lamb?

        When the Bridegroom cometh will your robes be white?
        Are you washed in the blood of the Lamb?
        Will your soul be ready for the mansions bright,
        And be washed in the blood of the Lamb?

        Lay aside the garments that are stained with sin,
        And be washed in the blood of the Lamb;
        There’s a fountain flowing for the soul unclean,
        O be washed in the blood of the Lamb!
"zzzxzz
    </string>
</resources>
